<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cfp | Nils Ole Tippenhauer</title>
    <link>https://tippenhauer.de/tags/cfp/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://tippenhauer.de/tags/cfp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Cfp</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://tippenhauer.de/images/icon_hua225200734429db22ec36f52bdb16dff_217603_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Cfp</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/tags/cfp/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: Wisec 2023</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-wisec-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-wisec-23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m co-chairing Wisec&#39;23 together with Brad Reaves. Please consider submitting, find the CfP below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;wisec23-call-for-papers&#34;&gt;Wisec&#39;23 Call for Papers&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Website: 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://wisec2023.surrey.ac.uk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://wisec2023.surrey.ac.uk/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact email: 
&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:wisec23-tpc-chairs@googlegroups.com&#34;&gt;wisec23-tpc-chairs@googlegroups.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submission link: 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://wisec23.hotcrp.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://wisec23.hotcrp.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 16th ACM Conference on Security and Privacy in Wireless and Mobile Networks (ACM WiSec 2023)
will be held physically from May 29 to June 1, 2023 in Guildford, UK. It is planned to be a fully in-person event if the COVID-19 pandemic situation allows this. Otherwise, the conference will be moved to the virtual space.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ACM WiSec is the leading ACM and SIGSAC conference dedicated to all aspects of security and privacy in wireless and mobile networks and their applications. In addition to the traditional ACM WiSec topics of physical, link, and network layer security, we welcome papers focusing on the increasingly diverse range of mobile or wireless applications such as Internet of Things, Cyber-Physical Systems, as well as the security and privacy of mobile software platforms, usable security and privacy, biometrics, and cryptography.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Topics of interest for WiSec include the following, concerning systems in the next second list below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confidentiality, integrity, availability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Authentication, identity, authorization, access control models and policies, localization,
key management (agreement or distribution),&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Privacy of systems, devices, users, their locations and other attributes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exploitation of systems, including through reverse engineering, fuzzing, hardware or
software vulnerabilities, protocol vulnerabilities, side channels, fault injection, resource
exhaustion, jamming, or other means.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Abuse of and through systems, including messaging abuse (spam, robocalls, etc.), theft
of service, and fraud&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defenses for exploitation and abuse&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experiences developing, testing, and deploying production-ready or large-scale secure
wireless systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formal analysis, formal verification, and proof-based security approaches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information theoretical approaches for security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usable security and privacy, human factors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Application of Machine Learning, e.g., for attack detection or privacy violations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Economic and social impacts to security and privacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wireless and Mobile Systems of Interest include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wireless networking protocols, for example: 802.11, Bluetooth, 802.15.4-based protocols, cellular air protocols including LTE and 5G-NR, Vehicle and industrial device protocols (e.g., LoRA), wireless for critical infrastructure (e.g., ADS-B, GPS, rail, satellites), NFC and smart payment applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cryptographic primitives and protocols for wireless and mobile systems, including: WPA2, AKA, &amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wireless physical layer technologies: transmission, reception, modulation, localization, remote sensing (e.g., radar, mmWave sensing), jammers, dynamic spectrum reuse and cognitive radio systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wireless and mobile device hardware and software, for example: embedded devices, wearables (e.g., watches), smartphones, mobile sensors, home and industrial automation devices (e.g., IoT, Smart Home, utilities, etc.), healthcare devices, vehicles (e.g., drones, automotive, avionics, satelites), and payment systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wireless and mobile adjacent topics, including voice interfaces, visible light communications, sonic, underwater communications, legacy telecommunications, &amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The proceedings of ACM WiSec, sponsored by SIGSAC, will be published by the ACM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;important-dates&#34;&gt;Important dates&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note: in 2023, WiSec will introduce two rounds of submission deadlines. In previous years, WiSec has had a tradition of announcing deadline extensions. Due to the change in submission process, there will be no extensions this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First submission round
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paper submission deadline: November 17th, 2022 (23:59 AoE) (no extensions)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Author notification: December 20th, 2022&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera-ready deadline: January 14th, 2023&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second submission round
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paper submission deadline: February 17th, 2023 (23:59 AoE) (no extensions)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Author notification: March 29th, 2023&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera-ready deadline: April 17th, 2023&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WiSec conference: May 29th to June 1st, 2023&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Papers rejected in the first round can be resubmitted to the second round. For such resubmissions, authors can choose to have the same reviewers and should provide a letter detailing revisions in that case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;submission-guidelines&#34;&gt;Submission Guidelines&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All papers for ACM WiSec 2023 must be submitted electronically through the HotCRP conference management system (
&lt;a href=&#34;https://wisec23.hotcrp.com/%29&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://wisec23.hotcrp.com/)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only PDF files will be accepted. Submissions must be prepared using the following ACM proceedings
template and must use US Letter page size (215.9 x 279.4 mm / 8.5 x 11 inches):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ACM proceedings template for LaTeX can be found at 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://wisec2023.surrey.ac.uk/cfp/acmart-1.80-wisec2022.zip&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://wisec2023.surrey.ac.uk/cfp/acmart-1.80-wisec2022.zip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Further information on ACM proceeding templates can be found at 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.acm.org/publications/proceedings-template&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.acm.org/publications/proceedings-template&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;full-short-and-sok-papers&#34;&gt;Full, short, and SoK papers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Full paper submissions to ACM WiSec 2023 can be up to 10 pages in the ACM conference style excluding the bibliography and well-marked appendices, and up to 12 pages in total. ACM WiSec also encourages the submission of short papers with a length of up to 6 pages (including bibliography and appendices), which describe mature work of a more succinct nature. All papers must be thoroughly anonymized for double-blind reviewing. Detailed submission instructions will be made available on the WiSec 2023 website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to regular papers that present novel contributions in the field, we solicit Systematization of Knowledge (SoK) papers that evaluate, systematize, and contextualize existing knowledge on any of the above topics. Suitable papers provide an important new viewpoint on an established research area, support or challenge long-held beliefs with compelling evidence, present a convincing new taxonomy of such an area, and/or identify research gaps with evidence and a structured approach. Survey papers without such contributions are not suitable. SoK submissions will be distinguished by the prefix &amp;ldquo;SoK:&amp;rdquo; in the title and a checkbox on the submission form. They can be up to 10 pages in the ACM conference style excluding the bibliography and well-marked appendices, and up to 15 pages overall. They will be reviewed by the program committee and held to the same standards as regular research papers, except instead of emphasizing novel research contributions the emphasis will be on value to the community. Accepted papers will be presented at the symposium and included in the proceedings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;opinion-papers&#34;&gt;Opinion papers&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ACM WiSec 2023 invites papers (ACM conference style, up to 3 pages excluding references) that present personal perspectives on all aspects of security and privacy in wireless and mobile networks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Opinion papers could also criticize previous research or research directions, as well as highlight possible promising research directions. The opinions expressed in these papers are expected to be anyway corroborated by theoretical foundations, experiments, or experiences. Like the regular papers, the opinion papers will be reviewed by the WiSec Technical Program Committee. The selected opinion papers will be a part of the WiSec technical program and will be published in the conference proceedings. Opinion papers should be submitted using the same submission procedure adopted for the full papers. The title of these papers must have the prefix &amp;ldquo;OPINION: &amp;ldquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;posters-and-demos&#34;&gt;Posters and demos&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WiSec will solicit submission of posters and demos. The instructions to submit posters/demos will be made available on the WiSec 2023 website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;artifact-evaluation-label&#34;&gt;Artifact Evaluation label&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the spirit of open science, WiSec encourages authors of accepted papers to make software and data artifacts publicly available to the community.
Such artifacts will be evaluated by the artifact evaluation committee and corresponding papers will be granted an artifact evaluation label. While artifacts are optional, their availability will be positively considered during paper evaluation. Should the authors choose to submit their artifacts for evaluation, they should indicate their decision upon paper submission and follow the artifact submission guidelines in order to submit them upon paper acceptance. The detailed guidelines will be made available on the WiSec 2023 website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;double-submissions&#34;&gt;Double submissions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a policy of the ACM to disallow double/simultaneous submissions, where the same (or substantially similar) paper is concurrently submitted to multiple conferences/journals. Any double submissions detected will be immediately rejected from all conferences/journals involved. Technical reports and pre-prints published online are allowed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;workshops-and-tutorial&#34;&gt;Workshops and Tutorial&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ACM WiSec will host workshops/tutorials co-organized with the main conference. Details will be made available on the website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;research-ethics&#34;&gt;Research Ethics&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ethical conduct of research is critical to ensuring the public trust and support of science. All submitted papers will be reviewed for ethical concerns, and if ethical practices were not followed a paper will be rejected regardless of any other merit. Ethical concerns vary from project to project, so there is no &amp;ldquo;one size fits all&amp;rdquo; approach. Rather, researchers should consider ethical analysis to be an integral part of the research, just as evaluation and method design are. Ethics should be considered early in a project, during a project, and as the project is prepared for publication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While every situation is unique, there are principles that researchers should consider and apply during their projects. The Menlo Report provides guidance and examples for network security. Principally, all research should embody the concepts of beneficence, justice, respect for persons, and respect of law and public interest. This is just as true for technical research as human subjects research. For example, if it is possible that a research method could cause harm to systems or users (e.g., testing jamming) researchers should explicitly detail the measures taken to prevent harm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research ethics is also paramount in any study that could be classified as &amp;ldquo;human subjects.&amp;rdquo; For WiSec, &amp;ldquo;human subject research&amp;rdquo; is defined as &amp;ldquo;research that involves interaction with identifiable humans or analysis of datasets containing data from one or more identifiable living humans.&amp;rdquo; Researchers are expected to follow the laws and common practices regarding human subjects review of their relevant jurisdictions and institutions. For example, researchers in the United States must undergo review by an Institutional Review Board (IRB) before beginning human subjects research. Authors doing human subjects research should mention the review standards in their jurisdictions and if they were met.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Computer security and privacy research often studies and even advances tools and techniques with the capacity to harm others. In their submission, authors must convince reviewers that appropriate steps were taken to disclose newly discovered vulnerabilities to appropriate parties&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;policy-for-peer-review-integrity&#34;&gt;Policy for Peer-Review Integrity&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All SIGSAC sponsored conferences and workshops are required to follow ACM policies against harassment activities (
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.acm.org/about-acm/policy-against-harassment&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.acm.org/about-acm/policy-against-harassment&lt;/a&gt;) and ACM Code of Ethics and Professional Conduct (
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.acm.org/code-of-ethics%29&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.acm.org/code-of-ethics)&lt;/a&gt;. Also all authors, PC members and non-PC reviewers are required to follow ACM Publications Policies (
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.acm.org/publications/policies/toc%29&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.acm.org/publications/policies/toc)&lt;/a&gt;. Particularly, we require all reviewers to uphold the integrity of the peer review process and avoid conflict of interest of any form (e.g., reviewer collusion ring). Those who violate these policies will be penalized according to ACM policies (
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.acm.org/publications/policies/penalties-for-publication-violations%29&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://www.acm.org/publications/policies/penalties-for-publication-violations)&lt;/a&gt;. If you would like to report a violation, please contact program chairs of your conferences/workshops or SIGSAC officers. We are committed to protecting the confidentiality of your communication.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: ACNS 2021</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-acns-21b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-acns-21b/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The second submission deadline for ACNS is coming up on Jan 15 AoE. Consider submitting your work! Details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;19th International Conference on Applied Cryptography and Network Security (ACNS)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;21-24 June 2021 in Kamakura, Japan (or online, if the situation requires)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://sulab-sever.u-aizu.ac.jp/ACNS2021/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;http://sulab-sever.u-aizu.ac.jp/ACNS2021/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Important Dates:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Submission Deadline 15 Jan 2021 AoE (Anytime on Earth)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Submission Notification 22 Mar 2021&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conference Date 21-24 June 2021&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: CPSS 2021</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cpss20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cpss20/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am co-chairing the 7th ACM Cyber-Physical System Security Workshop (CPSS 2021)
next year, together with Mauro Conti. CPSS is a long established workshop for
research on security of Cyber-Physical Systems (such as medical devices,
manufacturing and industrial control, robotics and autonomous vehicles). The
workshop will run for the seventh time, co-located with ASIACCS (7 June &amp;lsquo;21, Hong Kong). We just released the 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://spritz.math.unipd.it/events/2021/CPSS&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; and the full

&lt;a href=&#34;https://spritz.math.unipd.it/events/2021/CPSS/CPSS_2021_files/CPSS_CFP2021.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CfP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submitted papers can be up to 12 pages including appendices and references. Submissions must use the ACM SIG Proceedings Templates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;important-dates&#34;&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paper Submission Deadline: Jan 27, 2021 (23:59 Anywhere on Earth time)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notification of Acceptance/Rejection: Feb 26, 2021&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera Ready Papers Due: March 15, 2021 (hard deadline, see notification mails)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: CPSS 2021</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cpss21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cpss21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am co-chairing the 7th ACM Cyber-Physical System Security Workshop (CPSS 2021)
next year, together with Mauro Conti. CPSS is a long established workshop for
research on security of Cyber-Physical Systems (such as medical devices,
manufacturing and industrial control, robotics and autonomous vehicles). The
workshop will run for the seventh time, co-located with ASIACCS (7 June &amp;lsquo;21, Hong Kong).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The submission deadline Januar 27 AoE. 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://easychair.org/my/conference?conf=cpss21&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Direct Submission Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More details on the 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://spritz.math.unipd.it/events/2021/CPSS&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; and the full

&lt;a href=&#34;https://spritz.math.unipd.it/events/2021/CPSS/CPSS_2021_files/CPSS_CFP2021.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CfP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submitted papers can be up to 12 pages including appendices and references. Submissions must use the ACM SIG Proceedings Templates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;important-dates&#34;&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paper Submission Deadline: Jan 27, 2021 (23:59 Anywhere on Earth time)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notification of Acceptance/Rejection: Feb 26, 2021&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera Ready Papers Due: March 15, 2021 (hard deadline, see notification mails)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serving as CPSS 2021 Program Co-Chair</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cpss-co-chair21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cpss-co-chair21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Together with the program chair Mauro Conti, I will serve as program co-chair for the 7th ACM Cyber-Physical System Security Workshop in 2021, to be held in Hong Kong (or online). We plan to release the CfP with all details on deadlines etc. in the next weeks. Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP ACNS 2021 deadline extension</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-acns-21-extended/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-acns-21-extended/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first round ACNS&#39;21 deadline is extended by
3 days until September 7th AoE due to unexpected outage of the
conference website. Submissions can be made via easychair directly at&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https://easychair.org/my/login_author?conference=250210&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://easychair.org/my/login_author?conference=250210&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For any questions regarding the submission or the conference, please
write to 
&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:acns2021-contact@googlegroups.com&#34;&gt;acns2021-contact@googlegroups.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Detailed formatting instructions are given below in this post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://sulab-sever.u-aizu.ac.jp/ACNS2021/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;http://sulab-sever.u-aizu.ac.jp/ACNS2021/index.html&lt;/a&gt; (should be reachable
again by Sept 7)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;important-dates&#34;&gt;Important Dates:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First Submission Deadline 7 Sept 2020 AoE (Anytime on Earth)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First Submission Notification 9 Nov 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Submission Deadline 15 Jan 2021 AoE (Anytime on Earth)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Submission Notification 22 Mar 2021&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conference Date 21-24 June 2021&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submissions are double-blind, LNCS format 20+10 pages. Papers rejected
at the first round can be submitted at the second round, together with a
response letter addressing the reviewer&amp;rsquo;s points.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;conference-topics&#34;&gt;Conference Topics&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Areas of interest for ACNS 2021 include but are not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Applied cryptography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automated security analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Biometric security/privacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain and cryptocurrencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cloud security/privacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complex systems security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critical infrastructure security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cryptographic primitives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cryptographic protocols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data protection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database/system security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Digital rights management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email, app and web security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Future Internet security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Human factors in security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identity management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IP protection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internet fraud, cybercrime&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Internet-of-Things (IoT) security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intrusion detection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Key management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Malware&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile/wireless/5G security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Network security protocols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Privacy/anonymity, PETs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Security/privacy metrics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Side channel attacks (e.g., microarchitectural, physical-layer)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trust management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ubiquitous security/privacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Usable security/privacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;submission-instructions&#34;&gt;Submission Instructions&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submissions must not substantially duplicate work that any of the
authors has published elsewhere or has submitted in parallel to any
other venue with formally published proceedings. Information about
submissions may be shared with program chairs of other conferences for
that purpose. Submissions must be anonymous, with no author names,
affiliations, acknowledgement or obvious references. Each submission
must begin with a title and short abstract. The introduction should
summarise the contributions of the paper at a level appropriate
for a non-specialist reader. All submissions must follow the original
LNCS format (see 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.springeronline.com/lncs&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;http://www.springeronline.com/lncs&lt;/a&gt;​ ) with a page limit
of 20 pages (incl. references) for the main part (reviewers are not
required to read beyond this limit) and 30 pages in total. Papers should
be submitted electronically in PDF format. Papers rejected at the first
round can be submitted at the second round (together with a response
letter). Submissions not meeting the submission guidelines risk
rejection without consideration of their merits. We encourage
submissions in LaTeX. Authors of accepted papers must guarantee that
their paper will be presented at the conference and must make a full
version of their paper available online. Note that the page limit
for camera-ready version is 20 pages with up to 10 additional pages of
Appendix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;conflicts-of-interests&#34;&gt;Conflicts of Interests&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We use the following definition on conflicts of Interest, based on
Usenix Security’20: The program co-chairs require cooperation from both
authors and program committee members to prevent submissions from being
evaluated by reviewers who have a conflict of interest. During the
submission process, we will ask authors to identify members of the
program committee with whom they share a conflict of interest. This
includes: (1) anyone who shares an institutional affiliation with an
author at the time of submission, (2) anyone who was the advisor or
advisee of an author at any time in the past, (3) anyone the author has
collaborated or published with in the prior two years, (4) anyone who is
serving as the sponsor or administrator of a grant that funds
your research, or (5) close personal friendships. For other forms of
conflict, authors must contact the chairs and explain the perceived
conflict. Program committee members who are in conflict of interest with
a paper, including program co-chairs, will be excluded from evaluation
and discussion of the paper by default.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;organizing-committee&#34;&gt;Organizing Committee&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;general-co-chairs&#34;&gt;General Co-Chairs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chunhua Su, University of Aizu, Japan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kauzma Omote, University of Tsukuba, Japan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;program-co-chairs&#34;&gt;Program Co-Chairs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kazue Sako, Waseda University, Japan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nils Ole Tippenhauer, CISPA, Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;publicity-chair&#34;&gt;Publicity Chair&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keita Emura, NICT, Japan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;workshop-chair&#34;&gt;Workshop Chair&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jianying Zhou, Singapore University of Technology and Design, Singapore&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;poster-chair&#34;&gt;Poster Chair&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Masaki Shimaoka, University of Tsukuba/SECOM CO., LTD., Japan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;program-committee&#34;&gt;Program Committee&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mitsuaki Akiyama, NTT, Japan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cristina Alcaraz, University of Malaga, Spain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Man Ho Au, The Hong Kong Polytechnic University, Hong Kong&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lejla Batina, Radboud Universiteit, Netherlands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alex Biryukov, University of Luxembourg, Luxembourg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alexandra Boldyreva, Georgia Tech, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ferdinand Brasser, TU Darmstadt, Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chris Brzuska, Aalto University, Finland&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alvaro Cardenas, University of California at Santa Clara, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sudipta Chattopadhyay, SUTD, Singapore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Xiaofeng Chen, Xidian University, China&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liqun Chen, University of Surrey, UK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jiska Classen, TU Darmstadt, Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hervé Debar, Télécom SudParis, France&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stéphanie Delaune, IRISA, France&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christian Doerr, TU Delft, Netherlands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nico Döttling, CISPA, Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;F. Betül Durak, Robert Bosch LLC, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karim Eldefrawy, SRI International, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zekeriya Erkin, TU Delft, Netherlands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Olga Gadyatskaya, Leiden University, Netherlands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Joaquin Garcia-Alfaro, Telecom SudParis, France&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paolo Gasti, New York Institute of Technology, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dieter Gollmann, TUHH, Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stefanos Gritzalis, University of the Aegean, Greece&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Xinyi Huang, Fujian Normal University, China&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Antoine Joux, Sorbonne, France &amp;amp; CISPA, Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ghassan Karame, NEC Laboratories Europe, Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stefan Katzenbeisser, Darmstadt, Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hiroaki Kikuchi, Meiji University, Japan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qi Li, Tsinghua University, China&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zhiqiang Lin, Ohio State University, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Joseph Liu, Monash University, Australia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Xiapu Luo, Hong Kong Polytechnic University, Hong Kong&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Emil Lupu, Imperial College, UK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Di Ma, University of Michigan, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mark Manulis, University of Surrey, UK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Takahiro Matsuda, AIST, Japan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sjouke Mauw, University of Luxembourg, Luxembourg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Catherine Meadows, Naval Research Laboratory, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nele Mentens, KU Leuven, Belgium&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Veelasha Moonsamy, Radboud University, Netherlands&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Satoshi Obana, Hosei University, Japan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Martín Ochoa,Cyxtera Technologies, Colombia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wakaha Ogata, Tokyo Institute of Technology, Japan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Miyako Okubo, NICT, Japan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roberto Di Pietro, HBKU, Qatar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christina Pöpper, New York University Abu Dhabi, UAE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aanjhan Ranganathan, Northeastern University, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Joel Reardon, University of Calgary, Canada&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruben Rios, University of Malaga, Spain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sushmita Ruj, ISI Kolkata, India&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mark Ryan, University of Birmingham, UK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rei Safavi-Naini, University of Calgary, Canada&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kazue Sako (co-chair), Waseda University, Japan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Steve Schneider, University of Surrey, UK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sooel Son, KAIST, Korea&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hung-Min Sun, National Tsing Hua University, Taiwan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Willy Susilo, University of Wollongong, Australia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pawel Szalachowski, SUTD, Singapore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qiang Tang, New Jersey Institute of Technology, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nils Ole Tippenhauer (co-chair), CISPA, Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Selcuk Uluagac, FIU, USA&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edgar Weippl, Vienna University of Technology, Austria&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christian Wressnegger, KIT, Germany&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kehuan Zhang, Chinese University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: ACNS 2021</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-acns-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-acns-21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first submission deadline for ACNS is coming up on Sept 4. Consider submitting your work! Details:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;19th International Conference on Applied Cryptography and Network Security (ACNS)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;21-24 June 2021 in Kamakura, Japan (or online, if the situation requires)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://sulab-sever.u-aizu.ac.jp/ACNS2021/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;http://sulab-sever.u-aizu.ac.jp/ACNS2021/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Important Dates:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First Submission Deadline 4 Sept 2020 AoE (Anytime on Earth)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First Submission Notification 9 Nov 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Submission Deadline 15 Jan 2021 AoE (Anytime on Earth)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Second Submission Notification 22 Mar 2021&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conference Date 21-24 June 2021&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serving as ACNS 2021 Program Co-Chair</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/acns-co-chair21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/acns-co-chair21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Together with the program chair Kazue Sako, I will serve as program co-chair for the 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://jianying.space/acns/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;19th International Conference on Applied Cryptography and Network Security (ACNS)&lt;/a&gt; in 2021, to be held in Japan. We plan to release the CfP with all details on deadlines etc. around May. Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: CPS-SPC 2019</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cps-spc19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cps-spc19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am co-chairing the ACM Workshop on Cyber-Physical Systems Security &amp;amp;
Privacy (CPS-SPC) this year, together with Avishai Wool. CPS-SPC aims
to be the premier workshop for research on security of Cyber-Physical
Systems (such as medical devices, manufacturing and industrial
control, robotics and autonomous vehicles). The workshop will run for
the fifth time, co-located with CCS (11 November, London, UK). We just
released the website (
&lt;a href=&#34;cps-spc.org&#34;&gt;cps-spc.org&lt;/a&gt;) and the full 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cps-spc.org/2019/cfp.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CfP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submitted papers can be up to 12 pages including appendices and references. Submissions must use the ACM SIG Proceedings Templates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;important-dates&#34;&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paper Submission Deadline: June 21, 2019 (23:59 Anywhere on Earth time)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notification of Acceptance/Rejection: Aug 7, 2019&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera Ready Papers Due: August 30, 2019 (hard deadline, see notification mails)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: CPS-SPC 2018</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cps-spc18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cps-spc18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am co-chairing the ACM Workshop on Cyber-Physical Systems Security &amp;amp; Privacy (CPS-SPC) this year, together with Awais Rashid. CPS-SPC aims to be the premier workshop for research on security of Cyber-Physical Systems (such as medical devices, manufacturing and industrial control, robotics and autonomous vehicles). The workshop will run for the fourth time, co-located with CCS (19 October, Toronto, Canada). We just released the website (
&lt;a href=&#34;https://cps-spc.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;cps-spc.org&lt;/a&gt;) and the full 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cps-spc.org/2018/cfp.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CfP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submitted papers can be up to 12 pages including appendices and references. Submissions must use the ACM SIG Proceedings Templates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;important-dates&#34;&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paper Submission Deadline: July 1, 2018 (23:59 Anywhere on Earth time)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notification of Acceptance/Rejection: July 30, 2018&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera Ready Papers Due: August 19, 2018&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accepted: CPS-SPC 2018</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/accepted-cps-spc18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/accepted-cps-spc18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This year, I will be Co-Chair for the workshop on Cyber-Physical Systems Security and PrivaCy (CPS-SPC), together with Awais Rashid. Our proposal for the workshop is now accepted at CCS, and we will send out the CfP soon. Tentative date of the workshop: 19 October 2018, Toronto, Canada.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: CANS 2017</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cans-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cans-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am on the TPC for the Conference on Cryptology and Network Security (CANS), and the CfP was released. CANS 2017 will be held in Hong Kong on November 30-December 2.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The submission should be at most 16 pages (LNCS). The conference will also consider short submissions of up to 8 pages for results that are preliminary or that simply require few pages to describe. Authors of regular submitted papers will indicate at the time of submission whether they would like their paper to also be considered for publication as a short paper (8 proceedings pages).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Important dates: Abstract deadline July 18, 2017, full paper on July 25&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: Esorics 2017</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-esorics-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-esorics-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am in the TPC of ESORICS 2017, and the 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ntnu.edu/web/esorics2017/call-for-papers&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;call for papers&lt;/a&gt; has been released. The conference will be held 11-15 September in Oslo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ESORICS is the annual European research event in Computer Security. The Symposium started in 1990 and has been held in several European countries, attracting a wide international audience from both the academic and industrial communities. Papers offering novel research contributions in computer security are solicited for submission to the Symposium. The primary focus is on original, high quality, unpublished research and implementation experiences. We encourage submissions of papers discussing industrial research and development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paper submission deadline: April 19&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: WiSec 2017</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-wisec-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-wisec-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m on the TPC for WiSec, and the 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://wisec2017.ccs.neu.edu/call-for-papers-posters-demos.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;call for papers&lt;/a&gt; has been released:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ACM WiSec is the leading ACM and SIGSAC conference dedicated to all aspects of security and privacy in wireless and mobile networks and their applications. In addition to the traditional ACM WiSec topics of physical, link, and network layer security, we welcome papers focusing on the security and privacy of mobile software platforms, usable security and privacy, biometrics, cryptography, and the increasingly diverse range of mobile or wireless applications such as Internet of Things, and Cyber-Physical Systems. The conference welcomes both theoretical as well as systems contributions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year, there are a couple of interesting formats:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full and short papers (12/6 pages ACM format)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opinion papers (3 pages)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reproducibility label (for results reproduced by third party)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WiSec also solicits submission of posters and demos.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abstract submission: March 13, 2017&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: SEMS 2017</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-sems-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-sems-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am on the TPC of SEMS 2017, held in between with IEEE S&amp;amp;P and EUROCRYPT 2017 in Paris. The CfP was just released. More info 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://sems2017.cs.ru.nl/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Embedded and mobile devices that provide security and crypto functionalities, and manage private and confidential data are omnipresent in our daily lives. Examples of such devices range from smart cards and RFID tags, to mobile phones, tablets, and IoT devices. Ensuring the security and privacy of these devices is a challenging problem, as witnessed by recent breaking of crypto and security systems used in mobile phones, car keys, and RFID-enabled cards. Typical threats to extract the keys include side-channel and fault analysis. Additionally, the vulnerabilities of the devices imply also privacy concerns. The operating systems supporting some of those devices, particularly mobile phones and tablets, but also IoT ones, have become very complex. Various sorts of malware present a constant threat for users. Although measures like application sandboxing take place, they also open the court for new attacks by constantly collecting and organizing sensitive information about the user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The workshop seeks submissions from academia and industry presenting novel research results on the following topics of interest:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Security architectures for embedded and mobile systems&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Physical (side-channel and fault) attacks on embedded and mobile systems&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Hardware security of mobile devices&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– (mobile) Malware detection and prevention&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Machine learning applications to highlight possible threats to user privacy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Privacy-preserving issues for mobile devices&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Secure localization and location privacy for mobile devices&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Security and privacy in the Internet of Things&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Secure execution environments (e.g., TrustZone, TPMs) on mobile devices&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;– Sensor spoofing attacks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The one-day workshop will include presentation of peer-reviewed papers and two renowned keynote speakers, Prof. Srdjan Capkun (ETH Zurich, Switzerland) and Prof. Bart Preneel (KU Leuven, Belgium).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Accepted papers will be published by IEEE as the proceedings in “IEEE EuroS&amp;amp;P Workshops”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Important dates:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Submission deadline: 17 December 2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Notification: 20 January 2017&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camera-ready submission: 13 February 2017&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Workshop: 30 April 2017&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: CPSS 2017</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cpss-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cpss-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am on the PC of the Cyber-Physical System Security Workshop (CPSS), and the 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://icsd.i2r.a-star.edu.sg/cpss17/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CfP&lt;/a&gt; was just released&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cyber-Physical Systems (CPS) consist of large-scale interconnected systems of heterogeneous components interacting with their physical environments. There are a multitude of CPS devices and applications being deployed to serve critical functions in our lives. The security of CPS becomes extremely important. This workshop will provide a platform for professionals from academia, government, and industry to discuss how to address the increasing security challenges facing CPS. Besides invited talks, we also seek novel submissions describing theoretical and practical security solutions to CPS. Papers that are pertinent to the security of embedded systems, SCADA, smart grid, and critical infrastructure networks are all welcome, especially in the domains of energy and transportation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submission deadline is December 1. CPSS will be held in conjunction with ACM AsiaCCS’17
Abu Dhabi, UAE, April 2, 2017.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Batadal announced</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/batadal-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/batadal-announced/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have now officially announced the 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://batadal.net/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;BATADAL&lt;/a&gt; competition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The BATtle of the Attack Detection ALgorithms (BATADAL) will objectively compare the performance of algorithms for the detection of cyber attacks in water distribution systems. Participants will contribute an attack detection algorithm for a given water network following a set of rules that determine the exact goal of the algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Training datasets are now available. Deadline for first participant submissions is October 2 2016&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: RFIDSEC 2016</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-rfidsec-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-rfidsec-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am on the TPC for the 12th Workshop on RFID and IoT Security (RFIDsec) 2016, and the call for papers was just released. Submission Date is 12 September 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Started in 2005, RFIDsec has become the premier venue devoted to security and privacy of Radio Frequency Identification (RFID). The nature of radio-enabled item identification and automatic data capture has significantly changed overthe years driven by the interest in overarching applications such as the Internet-of-Things and cyber-physical systems. As such, RFIDsec has also broadened its scope and seeks papers describing any contributions to security and privacy in any application area related to any constrained wireless devices, such as sensor nodes, smart wearables, contactless smart cards, programmable logic controllers (PLCs) and RFID tags.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More details 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://rfidsec2016.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: APS-CPS 2016</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-aps-cps-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-aps-cps-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m on the PC for the “Automation Protocols Security in Cyber-Physical Systems” (APS-CPS), held in conjunction with ICNP  2016 in Singapore on Nov 8 2016 – 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.aps-cps.org/callforpapers.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;. The deadline was just extended to July 30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The International Workshop on Automation Protocols Security in Cyber-Physical Systems (APS-CPS) seeks novel submissions describing practical and theoretical solutions to securing automation protocols. Submissions may represent any application area for APS-CPS. Hence, papers that are pertinent to the security of embedded systems, Internet of Things, SCADA Systems, Smart-Grid Systems, Critical Infrastructure Networks, Transportation Systems, Medical Devices are all welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: SG-CRC 2017</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-sg-crc-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-sg-crc-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m on the TPC for the Singapore Cyber Security R&amp;amp;D Conference (SG-CRC) 2017, and the CfP was just released. The conference will be held in Singapore on 21-22 February 2017 at the National University of Singapore (NUS). More details here. The conference’s theme is “Systems Approach to Cyber Security”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This conference will bring together academics and practitioners from across the world to participate in a vibrant programme consisting of research papers, industrial best practices, and tools exhibition. This conference focus on techniques and methodologies oriented to construct resilient systems against cyber-attacks that will helps to construct safe execution environments, improving security of both hardware and software by means of using mathematical tools and engineering approaches for designing, verifying, and monitoring cyber physical systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;important-dates&#34;&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research Track Deadline: 1 October 2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Practice Track Deadline: 8 October 2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Acceptance Notification: 15 November 2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Final Version Deadline: 1 December 2016&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers: SCSP-W 2016</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-scspw-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-scspw-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m on the TPC for the “Smart City Security and Privacy Workshop” (SCSP-W 2016), held in conjunction with CPS Week 2016 in Vienna, Austria on 11-14 April, 2016 – link.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CPS Week is the premier event on Cyber-Physical Systems and brings together academicians, industry experts, and government representatives from around the world. The SCSP-W workshop will focus on security and privacy aspects of smart cities that are pertinent to areas like Internet of Things (IoT), Smart Buildings, Smart‑Grid Systems, Critical Infrastructure Networks, Intelligent Transportation Systems, and Medical Devices. SCSP-W is a full day workshop and will include research papers, invited talks, and discussion sessions to facilitate exchange of research ideas in a community environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submission deadline: January 822, 2016&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers: IFIP SEC 2016</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-ifip-sec-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-ifip-sec-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m on the TPC for the 31th IFIP TC-11 SEC 2016 International Information Security and Privacy Conference. Its CfP was just released, more details here. Deadline for paper submissions is December 24, 2015. From the CfP:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The IFIP SEC conference is the flagship event of the International Federation for Information Processing (IFIP) Technical Committee 11 on Security and Privacy Protection in Information Processing Systems(TC-11, 
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ifiptc11.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;www.ifiptc11.org&lt;/a&gt;  ). Previous SEC conferences were held in Hamburg (Germany) 2015, Marrakech (Morroco) 2014, Auckland (New Zealand) 2013, Heraklion (Greece) 2012, Lucerne (Switzerland) 2011, and Brisbane (Australia) 2010. We seek submissions from academia, industry, and government presenting novel research on all theoretical and practical aspects of security and privacy protection in ICT Systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CfP: SG-CRC 2016</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-sg-crc-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-sg-crc-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are organizing the inaugural Singapore Cyber Security R&amp;amp;D Conference (SG-CRC) in 2016. The call for papers is now available 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://itrust.sutd.edu.sg/sg-crc-2016/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;online&lt;/a&gt;, deadline for papers is October 26, 2015. About the conference:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The conference will bring together academics and practitioners from across the world to participate in a vibrant program consisting of research papers,  industrial best practices, and tools exhibition. Students, undergraduate and graduate are encouraged to participate in specially organized sessions.  Several cash awards and certificates will be given to the best contributions in various categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Papers: CPSS 2016</title>
      <link>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cpss-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tippenhauer.de/post/cfp-cpss-2016/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m on the TPC for the 2nd ACM Cyber-Physical System Security Workshop. Its CfP was just released, more details 
&lt;a href=&#34;http://icsd.i2r.a-star.edu.sg/cpss16/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Deadline for paper submissions is December 5, 2015. From the CfP:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cyber-Physical Systems (CPS) consist of large-scale interconnected
systems of heterogeneous components interacting with their
physical environments. There are a multitude of CPS devices and
applications being deployed to serve critical functions in our
lives. The security of CPS becomes extremely important. This
workshop will provide a platform for professionals from academia,
government, and industry to discuss how to address the increasing
security challenges facing CPS. Besides invited talks, we also
seek novel submissions describing theoretical and practical
security solutions to CPS. Papers that are pertinent to the
security of embedded systems, SCADA, smart grid, and critical
infrastructure networks are all welcome, especially in the domains
of energy and transportation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
